Guide to the Montana State Prison records 1864-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Montana State Prison
  - Prisoner Records
    - Prisoner description sheets: V.L. Radcliffe, Clifford Rader, Durward Ragan, Charles Raines, Charles Ralston, William Ralston, Frank Ramos, Idema Ramsey, Winfreid Ramsay, C.E. Randell, Frank Randerhoff, James Randle, Keith Randolph, Irwin Rasch, Dan Raspberry, Christian Rassmussen, Charles O. Rathe, Allen Ray, Wilber Ray, C.H. Raymond, Harry Raymond, John Raymond, Edward Rays, Angus C. Read, Eugene Ready, James Reagan, W.H. Rector, Willie Redboy, Charles Reed, Charles E. Reed, Don Reed, F.G. Reed, Edward Reed, George Reed, James Reed, Harold K. Reed, L.E. Reed, Jay Reeder, Charles Reese, Matt Reese, Clyde Reeves, Robert Reeves, Charles Reid, Edward Regan, Charles Reid, W.J. Reidy, Jim Reilly, Joe Reilly, Oscar Rein, Joe Reiser, Fred Remheckl, Joe Rems, James Renahan, Mike Remik, Leo Reno, William Reno, David B. Renz, George Ressler, George Revore, Ed Reyes, Claude Reynolds, E.O. Reynolds, Frank J. Reynolds, J.L. Reynolds, Jesse Reynolds, Richard Ray Reynolds, William Reynolds, William Rhine, George E. Rhoades, Jefferson Rhoads, J.T. Rhodes, J.H. Rhys, Frank Rice, John Rice, Fred Richards, Pearl Richards, J.A. Richardson, Joseph W. Richardson, Leonard Richardson, Lewis Richeleau, Robert Rickerby, Joe Rico, Emmett Riddle, Edward Ruley, John Rife, George T. Riggs, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Tony Rihas, Frank Riley, George Riley, Jack Riley, James Riley, James Riley, Ralph Riley, Thomas B.O.Riley Jr., John W. Rimassa, Norman Rindahl, Albert Ringle, Charles Ringo, John Risbin, Otto Ristoe, John L. Ritchie, Robert Ritchie, Thomas Ritchie, Alberto Rivas, John M. Rivas, E.A. Rivers, John Roach, John Roach, C.A. Roberts, Edward Roberts, Fred Roberts, James Roberts, Joe Roberts, Virgil Roberts, William Roberts, W.H. Roberts, George Robertson, J.W. Robertson, Joseph Robertson, Lawrence Robertson, L.M. Robinett, Andrew Robinson, Arthur O. Robinson, Avery Robinson, C.C. Robinson, Charles Robinson, Clyde Robinson, Clyde Herbert Robinson, D.J. Robinson, Frank Robinson, George Robinson, George Robinson, Henry Robinson, James Robinson, Lee Robinson, James Robinson, Peter C. Robinson, A.W. Robinson, Louie Rochileau, Little Rock, John Rodak, Bruce Rodehaven, Fred Rodewald, Fred Rodewald, Esequill Rodriguez, Carlos Rodriguez, Cresceniano Rodriguez, Manuel Rodriguez, E.R. Roe, Jack Roe, William Roemer, George F. Rogan, E.B. Rogers, George Rogers, Harry Rogers, J.P. Rogers, John L. Rogers, John P. Rogers, Oscar Rogers, P.I. Rogers, William Rogers, Stephen Rogorinski, Herman Rohde, August Rohlfs, Brendon Rohn, Antonio Rojo, E.E. Rollins, Edward E. Rollins, James Romans, Domenico Romeo, Ed Romstad, Sam Roof, Gene Rooker, Richard Roos, John Root, Nathanial Root, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 52/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Bert Rose, Benjamin Rose, James Rose, Leonard S. Rose, Richard Rose, Sam Rose, Leon Roseburg, Gustav Roselund, Frank Roseman, Leon Rosenbery, Leon Rosenberg, C. Ross, Charles A. Ross, Edward Ross, Patrick Ross, Gus Rossman, Joe Rosso, George Roueques, C.A. Rowell, Edward Rowland, Henry C. Rowland, William C. Roy (alias William C. King, Nathan Rubenstein, John Ruck, Oscar Rudd, John Ruddy, Frank Rudock, Fay Rumsey, W.S. Runkle, William Rush, Bert Russell, George Russell, Harry Russell, James Russell, Selmer Russett, L.C. Ruyle, B.N. Ryan, B.W. Ryan, Clem Ryan, Dan Ryan, Frank Ryan, Fred Ryan, George Ryan (alias Carroll Palmer), Harry Ryan, James Ryan, John B. Ryan, Thomas Ryan, Thomas Ryan, Thomas (Buddy) Ryan, Thomas Ryan, William Ryan, Ernest P. Sackse, Fred Lager, Fred Saindon, S. Sakaguchi, Isaac Salmonsen, W.G. Sallas, John Salo, John Samaras, William Sampson, Dominecko San Antonio, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 53/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Nick Sanchelli, Edward Sanford, George Sanieto, E.B. Santos, Joe Santrosa, Frank Sapp, Matt Sappi, H.A. Sargent, John Sargent, John O. Sargent, Nicholas Sasso, Theodore Satre, Albert E. Saunders, John Saunders, Benjamin T. Savage, John Saxberg, Charles Saylor, Charley D. Schad, Edward Schad, Elliott Schadinger, John Schirmer Jr., Herman Schli, Carl Schmalhaus, John Schmidt, Lawrence Schmidt, Tom Schmidt, Carl Ferdinand Schnittger, Earnest Schriber, Paul Schroeder, W.L. Schroder, Albert M. Schubert, Charles Schubert, Frank Schuch (alias F.S. Schulen), Frank Schuch, Carl Schultz, William F. Shultz, Ray Schumaker, Ray B. Schumacher, Carl Schultz, Frank J. Schurtz, Joe Schutt, Albert Scott, Cammie Scott, F.H. Scott, Frank Scott, F.S. Scott, Sam J. Scott, W.H. Scott, Walter Scott, Walter Scott, William Scott, William Scott, Wright Scott, Frank Scrivner, Clarence S. Scudder, William Scully, Fred Seals, John F. Sears, Nebrone Selido, N.W. Shadon, Emmett Shandy, William Shannon, A.M. Shaver, Michael Shaughnessy, Clinton Shaver, Fred Herman Shaver, Gilbert Shaver, Charles L. Shaw, Ed Shaw, Fred A. Shaw, Harry Shaw, James L. Shaw, Ed Shea, James Shea, Mike Shea, Thomas M. Shea, William Shear, Mat Sheehan, Chauncey A. Sheldon, Henry Shelly, Ollie Shelton (alias Sam Johnson), Ed Sheridan, Almon Sherlock, Lee Sherry, R.G. Sheubert, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 53/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: John D. Shields, Ben Winters Shirk, Frank Shong, Oscar Dana Short, Bert Shufelt, Gus L. Siamolton, A.J. Sicklestell, Charles Sicora, Herman Sieben, John Henry Sieben, John Michael Sieben, Louis Sieff, Adolph Sigrist, Joe Silva, Lewis A. Silver, J.B. Simmons, William Simmons, George Simms, Andrew Simonson, Frank Simpson, Harold D. Simpson, Frank Simms, Ruth Simms, John Simpson, Dan Sims, Frank Sims, Jack Sinclair, Fred Singleton, Mike Siperaro, Louis Sisco, Louis Sittig, Andrew Siveljch, Andrew Siveljch, George Skarpas, Alfred Skeel, Carl Skeie, C.C. Skidmore, Albert Skiell, William Skillhorn, Earl Slater, John J. Slater, John S. Slaughter, Mike Slezinger, John Slobodzian, Grover Cleveland Slocum, J.H. Slothower, Adrian Smit, Alfred Smith, Anthony Smith, Anthony Smith, Bert Smith, C.B. Smith, Charles Smith, Charles Smith, Charles Smith, Charles F.A. Smith, Charles W. Smith, Daniel Smith, Dennie M. Smith, Doe Smith, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: E.J. Smith, Earl Smith, Edd Smith, Edward Smith, Edward P. Smith, Floyd Smith, Frank Smith, Frank Smith, Frank Smith, Frank Smith, Frank Smith, Frank L. Smith, George Smith, George Smith, George W. Smith, Guy Smith, Harry Smith, Harry Smith, Henry Smith, James J. Smith, Janet Smith, Jess Smith, Joe Smith, Joe Smith, John Smith, John Smith, John Smith, John Smith, John Smith, John Smith, John Smith, John L. Smith, John R. Smith, John R. Smith, Max Smith, Mike Smith, Mike Smith, Mytle Smith, Norman Smith, Oscar Smith, Oscar Smith, Otto Smithman, Owen Smith, P.R. Smith, Paul Smith, Ralph Smith (alias B. Waldo), Robert Smith, Robert H. Smith, Sam Smith, Tom Smith, Toy Smith, W.H. Smith, W.K. Smith, William Henry Smith, William Smith, John Snopek, Clarence Snyder, Fred Snyder, John H. Snyder, Lee Snyder, Jack Soda, Fred Sohl, Fred Sohl, Bert Solley, Francis L. Soria, J.D. Sorrel, Joe Soto, Arthur M. Spackman, Cyrus A. Spangler, R.C. Spangler, James Spanos, J.S. Spaulding, Walter Spaulding, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 53/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: John Spearois, J.A. Speck, John H. Speiser, Elmer Spencer, Floyd Spencer, Jack Spencer, John Spies, Tom Spilios, Charles P. Spinharney, William Le Vant Spitzer, George Spivens, A.L. Spooner, Henry Spooner, Walter A. Spurrier, Frank St Clair (alias Frank Ward), Norman St Clair, William St Clair, William St Clair, A.J. St John, H.E. Stanley, Henry Starks, James H. Stamper, John Stafford, A.B. Stavrapulos, Henry Stairs, Harry Stanley, Roy Starbeck, Guy Stanich, Frank Stack, William Starner, E.V. Starr, Thomas H. Staggs, Bruce Stacey, Adam Steck, Guy Stanich, Henry Steinman, C. Steele, James Steele, William Steen, Harry Stem, A.H. Stender, Fred Stephens, T.F. Stephens, William Stephenson, John Stetson, Charles Stevens, M.C. Stevens, Henry Stevens, M.C. Stevens, Frank Stevens, Ralph P. Stevens, H.C. Stevens, George Q. Stevenson, Peter Stevenson, Dee Steward, George Steward, Patrick Stewart, Max Stewart, William Stewart, Lee Stewart, Lee Stewart, Grant Stewart, William Stewart, Grant Stewart, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Prisoner description sheets: F.M. Stice, Bert Stidham, Fred Stidham, Henry F. Stienke, Lee Stiles, Harry Stine, Noah Stine, William Stinebrink, L.W. Stocker, Earl Stauffer, Paul Stokie, Otto Stone, Everette J. Stoner (alias E.J. Monehan), Enoch Stoops, Butler R. Storke, Charles W. Stothart, A.J. Straten, Roscoe Stratton, Robert Strayton, Earl Streater, Joseph Stroud, Frank Strnad, Levi J. Stuart, Arthur H. Sturges, John Sturlino, Jack Stuart, Harold Sturdal (alias Sam Simpson), Bert Sturgis, Al Stuart, Bert Sturgis, John Subrtes, C.O. Sugden, Walter Sugden, Strawley Sugg, Louis Suhr, George Sullivan, James Sullivan, James E. Sullivan, John Sullivan, John Sullivan, John F. Sullivan, John J. Sullivan, Michael Sullivan, Pat Sullivan, Patrick Sullivan, Patrick Sullivan, Sylvester Sullivan, William Sullivan, Jake Sully, Albert Summers, Edward Summers, John Sumption, Otto Sundell, Toy Sunt, Buda Suput, Tom Surle, Alexander Sutherland, J. Suttey, E.L. Sutton, John Swain, Joseph Swan, Art Swanson, George Swanson, J.C. Swanson, Charles Swartz, James W. Sweeney, William Swink, Paul Swisher, Frank Syriax, Mike Szasz, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 54/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: John Taffner, Robert Taintor, William Tait, Olin Talbott, Ira Talbott, Ed Talley, Joe Tanicuchi, William Tamley, Edward Tanquary, John Taplan, Tex Tarfety, Joseph Henry Tarr, D.E. Tate, A.W. Taylor, Buck Taylor, Charles Taylor, Ed Taylor, George Taylor, H.A. Taylor, H.A. Taylor, H.C. Taylor, James A. Taylor, James A. Taylor, John Taylor, John Taylor, Llyod Taylor, Ray Taylor, Sid J. Taylor, Theodore Taylor, W.D. Taylor, W.H. Taylor, John Temple, C.E. Thayer, Donald Thayer, John Thayer, Harry Theodore, Ernest Therrault, Joseph T. Thibadeau, Charles Tholing, Arthur Thom, Alex Thomas, Anthony Thomas, David Thomas, E.H. Thomas, Franklin Thomas, George Thomas, Griff Thomas, Harry B. Thomas, Joseph Thomas, L.C. Thomas, Patsy Thomas, Ted Thomas, Walter Thomas, Alex Thompson, Ed Thompson, Ernest Thompson, Frank Thompson, George Thompson, Frank Thompson (Ed King), Frank Thompson, George Thompson, George Thompson, Harley Thompson, Harry Thompson, J.H. Thompson, J.C. Thompson, Louis Thompson, Myrtle Thompson, Patsy Thompson, Roy Thompson, J.A. Thompson, Thomas Thompson, Thomas Thompson, Urban Thompson, Walter Thompson, Walter Thompson, William Thompson, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Frank Thornton, B.S. Thresher, Roy Thurman, Bert H. Thurston, James Thurston, Edward Tibbetts, W.J. Tice, James L. Tiddy, A.D. Timmerman, Mike Teschner, Loren Tolbert, Lazar Tomich, Kosto Toomkovich, E.J. Tompkins, Toy Tong, Margaret Torma, Tom Torros, M.B. Toutsch, A.J. Towey, E.B. Towne, Albert Townsend, Grover Tracey, H.N. Tracy, Thomas Tracey, Fred Tracy, Frank Tracy, Gust Trebes, L.L. Tressler, Clinton Tripp, Tora Trist, Joseph Trochie, Robert Troppman, William Troutman, John F. Trumbo, Overton Tudor, Alfred Turcott, Earl Turner, George Turner, Harry Turner, Paul Turner, Joseph Turner, Owen Twohey, Edward Charles Tyler, Frederich G. Tyree, Charles Underwood, Judson Underwood, W.B. Updyke, Rade Uselich, James David Usher, John M. Usher, L.W. Usher (alias W.F. Williams), Rinaldi Valle, Antone Vallie, Oliver Van, Thomas Van Buren, Arthur Vanderbilt, Arthur Vanderbilt, Walter Vandervoort, John Van Dolah, Joe Van Duren, Abraham Vangoor, Peter VanGurp, L.N. Vanhorn, J.M. Van Horn, S. Van Houten, George Van Laningham, John Vannoy, Burton J. Van Orman, Frank Van Sant, J. Van Skelton, Floyd Van Winkle, Elmer Varner, Auditich Vasel, George Vasel, Sam Vaughn, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Jean Marie Veilleux, R. Verlind, J.N. Verdon, J.W. Vernell, E.J. Vicain, George Vickers, Albert E. Victor, Mike Villano, Frank Vinn, J.J. Virgin, William Vitalis, Fred Vogel, Ivan Vojvodich, Clarence J. Voss, Audryo Vuhovich, Anton Vonelsen, M. Vucovich, Frank Waara, Heney Waarum, Fred Waddington, Hoyt Wade, Jerry W. Waggner, Charles E. Wagner, Edward Wagner, Edward Wagner (alias Edward Dusseau), Alfred Waight, Robert Waining, Frank Walden, Eberhard Waldru, Ed Walker, G.W. Walker, H. Walker, H.N. Walker, Harry Walker, Sam Walker, George Wallace, J.A. Wallace, Joe Wallace, Peter Wallace, William Wallace, John H. Waller, Frank Wallette, George Wallette, J.A. Walters, George A. Walton (alias George Mills), Harry Walton, Lee Walton, R.G. Walton, Charles Ward, Frank Ward, Harry L. Ward, Nathaniel Ward, Richard Ward, Richard Ware, Charles Warner, Charles Warner, Lawrence Warner, Ed Warren, Thomas Warren, George W. Washington, Earl E. Waters, Edwin Edgar Waters, Dennis Watkins, Allen Watson, Earl Watson, George Watson, James Watson, Joseph William Watson, Frank Watts, Clyde Waumble, Paul Wauthier, Charles Weasel Head, Jack Weathers, Jesse Weaver, Frank Weedon, August Wegner, Martin Wehinger, Earl Welch, James Welch, Roy Welever, Chauncey Wells, George A. Wells, John A. Wells, L.L. Wells, Frank Welsh, James Welch, William Welsh, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: William Wenberg, Oliver Wentz, Frank West, Glen F. West, Jack West, Lee F. West, W.E. West, Karl Westerlund, P.F. Westfall, Axel Westling, A.B. Weston, Chauncey D. Weston, John Weyrick, Fred Wheeler, Victor E. Wheeler, W.L. Wheeler, Nathan Whipple, John A. Whitby, O.B. Whitcomb, Ray Whitcomb, Charles White, Clay White, George White, Gustav White, Harry White, Homer White, James White, John White, M.D. White, Neal White, Robert White, Stanly White, Will White, John Whiting, John A. Whitting, Frank Whitlock, H.F. Whitlock, Joseph A. Whitman, Charles Whitney, Walter Whitworth, W.B. Wicks, A.D. Wiggins, Albert Darwin Wiggins, Thomas Wiggins, Frank Wilbert, Frank Wilcox, Harley Wilcox, Herbert Wilcox, Leonard Wilcox, John Wildely, B.S. Wiley, T.M. Wiley, Ted Wilkerson, W.O. Wilkerson, J.A. Wilkes, Fred Willard, George Willette, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Aaron Williams, Al Williams, Arthur Williams, Charles Williams, Clay Williams, Ed Williams, Ed Williams, Ed Williams, Ed Williams, Edwin Williams, Frank Williams, Frank Williams, Frank Williams, Fred Williams, Fred D. Williams, George Williams, George Williams, George Williams, George Williams, George Williams, George Williams, George L. Williams, H.B. Williams, Harry Williams, J.H. Williams, James Williams, James Williams, John Williams, John Williams, John Williams, John Williams, John Williams, John E. Williams, P.H. Williams, Ray Williams, Robert Williams, Roy Williams, Tom Williams, W.H. Williams, William Williams, Foster Williamson, John Willie, Frank Willis, James Willis, Joseph Willis, Wyatt Willis, Fred Wills, Fred Wilsdorf, B.L. Wilsey, Bob Wilson, Ed Wilson, Floyd Wilson, Frank Wilson, Frank Wilson, Frank Wilson, Frank Wilson, Fred Wilson, Fred Wilson (alias Charles Thompson), Fred Wilson, George Wilson, George Wilson, George Wilson, Harry T. Wilson, Jack Wilson, James Wilson, Jim Wilson, John Wilson, John Wilson, John Wilson, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Lee Wilson, Lester Wilson, M.B. Wilson, Ray Wilson, Roscoe Wilson, Roy Wilson, S.H. Wilson, S.M. Wilson, W.R. Wilson, William Wilson, Gus Winburn, William Winchester, S.R. Windiate, Helsten Wing, Curtis G. Wingerd, Charles Wingfield, Edward Winship, Albert Winters, Samuel Wisemiller, Harry Wisner, Temple Witham, Frank Wolf, Harry Peter Wolf, Rosa Wolf, John Woller, Charles Wood, Earl Stanley Woodbury, Denver Woods, Oscar Woods, Samuel F. Woodard, Price Woods, Charles Woodward, Charles Working, E.B. Worley, George Worley, Steve Worley, Robert L. Worth, Frank G. Wray, Charles H. Wright, Floyd Wright, Frank Wright, Fred Wright, James Wright, W.L. Wright, Wladystaw Wrono, Fred Wyman, A. Wynne, Owen Wynne, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Vernie Yaeger, G. Yamamoto, H.L. Yandell, Bob Yates, Bert L. Yeager, Fred Yeuthery, Albert Yiek, Quon Ying, Jacob Yli, Arthur Yoder, Archie Young, Charles Young, Charles W. Young, Clarence B. Young, Frank Young, Fred Young, James Young, Louis Young, Robert Young, Thomas Young, Zenon Yriarte, Hong Chai Yuen, Frank Zach, William Henry Zeller, A.S. Ziddons, Ernest Zielke, Mike Zielke, August Zimmerman, Tom Zimmerman, George Zulevitch, P.L. Zwibel, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: John Aaboe Jr., John Ankre, Charles Abbot, Frank Abbott, Herbert Abbott (alias Frank Peterson), D.J. Abel, Harry G. Abel, Robert Abel, Joe Abell, Guy E. Abernathy, Charles E. Abraham, Jay Acebedo, Rolin Acherman, Robert F. Ackerman, William Ackerman, Voy Ackroyd, Leo Acosta, Edward M. Acquin, Alex Adams, Charles Adams, Charles Adams, Clyde I. Adams, David Adams, Earl T. Adams, Frank Adams, J. Adams, James C. Adams, James L. Adams, Jess Adams, John Adams, Joseph Francis Adams Jr., Orville Adams, Ralph Daniel Adams, Wilbur Almond Adams, William Adams, William Adams, Kermit Adamson, Earl Addison, Richard Addison, George Ade, Louis Adler, Joseph J. Adrian, Fred Age, Sam Agee, Tommy Aglular, Thomas William Agnew, Antonio Aguilar, John Ahlbin, Howard Ahrens, Howard Ahrens, Kenneth Dean Ahrenkiel, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Clarence E. Aichele, August Aiello, Frank Aikens, George Aikens, Jack Aiker, William Nevils Aiman, Francis Aims Back, Raymond Aims Back, Clifford Akerill, Norman R. Akerill, Hugh Akers, John Akers, Orville N. Akers, William C. Akin, Desiderio Alarcon, Paul Irving Alban, Mararito Albarado, Edmond Albertson, George Albertson (alias Charles Busetta), H.R. Albrecht, Lloyd Albrecht, Robert Alcorn, Joe Aldaco, Warren Alden, Emanuel Aldena, B.E. Alderman, Thomas Aldridged, Tom Alefteras, A.C. Alexander, Albert Alexander, Donald Alexander, Donald L. Alexander, Duane Alexander, Eugene Alexander, Peter H. Alexander, Roy Alexander, William Alexander, Anthony F. Alexandrowski, Inonsencio Alfara, Algie W. Alford, Edward Ferdinand Alimendinger, T.C. Allan, Albert Allen, Albert G. Allen, Arliss Allen, Arthur Allen, Carl Allen, Doris Harold Allen, Eugene Allen, Eugene F. Allen, Fred Allen, Frank Allen, Garnet Allen, Gene Allen, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Glenn Allen, Harry Allen, Harry Allen, Hugh Allen, James Allen, Jim Allen (alias Earl Powell), Joe Allen, Joseph Allen, Joseph E. Allen, Phillip Jack Allen, Robert Allen, Roy Allen, Roy Allen, Roy F. Allen, Russell E. Allen, Scott Allen, Theodore Allen, Tom Allen, Joe Allery, Thomas Lee Alley, John Henry Alley, James Allison, James A. Allison, Ervin Alan Allmer, Jacob Allmer, Jake Allmer, Murphy Lee Allran, Howard Andrew Allum, Vernon I. Allyn, Raymond Allyson, Rafael Almendarez, Healy Aloir, Joe Alonzo, Russell Alsop, George Alton, George E. Alton, Joe Altona, Joe Alvaraz, Juan Alvarez, Agapito Alvary, Jose Alvers, James Ambrose, Clifford Amdahl, Francis Ameline, Neil A. Amerman, Edwin H. Ames Sr., Marvin Lloyd Ames, Angel Amicay, Mervin Amick, Fred Ammeline, Jerry A. Amor, Emmett Clark Amos, John Patrick Amyotte, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Colestino Anaya, Ace Anderson, Albert Anderson, Albert H. Anderson, Alfred Anderson, Arnold Anderson, Arthur Anderson, Arthur Anderson, Arthur Elihua Anderson, Arthur Rupert Anderson (alias Art Anderson), Boyd Anderson, Bruce Anderson, Carl George Anderson, Chester E. Anderson, Claude Anderson, Donald Howard Anderson, Erick Anderson, Francis Anderson, Frank Anderson, George Anderson, George Anderson, Gerald Anderson, Gerald A. Anderson, Harold Anderson (alias Harold McManus), Harold Anderson, Harold Anderson, Jack Anderson, James Anderson, John C. Anderson, L.H. Anderson, Lester Anderson, M.L. Anderson, Matthew Leonard Anderson, Norman L. Anderson, Oliver Anderson, Paul Anderson, Paul A. Anderson, Robert George Anderson, Roy Anderson, Russell Anderson, Stanley E. Anderson, Vernon Anderson, W.H. Anderson, Walter Anderson, William Anderson, William T. Anderson, Charles Andrew, Fred Andrew, Steve Andrewpenkl, Bob Andrews, George Anderews, James Andrews, James Andrews, Louis Andriopoulos, Lee Andrus, R.L. Andrus, Washburn H. Andrus, Tony Aneso, Albert Angelo, Thurman L. Anglin, Genaro Anguiano, Rafael Anguiano, Martin Ankney, Antone Matt, Frank Antonich, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Joe E. Aragon, Julian R. Aranda, Merville Archambeau, Virgil Chandler Archbell, Samuel Edmund Archdale, Joe Archuleto, Paul Joseph Archuletta, Jim Arellano, Renato Romano Arena, Pablo Ariaz, Stark Arklow, Alva Armstrong, David Price Armstrong, Dean E. Armstrong, George Armstrong, Paul Frank Armstrong, Roy Armstrong, Roy Warren Armstrong, Walter C. Armstrong, William Armstrong, Helmer Arness, A.H. Arnold, Albert Arnold, Ben Arnold, Charles Thomas Arnold, Frankie Arnold, Harry Rex Arnold, Paul Arnold, Wayne Arnold (alias Wayne Earl Ellis), Lee Arrigoni (alias Ruby Garrett), Victor George Arrison, Lester Arthur, William Clarence Arthur, Robert Arthurs, George Asbury, Leo R. Asbury, Max Asencio, Marvin Ash, Violet Ash, Harry Asher Jr., Mary Asher, Guy Ashley, Harless Ashley, William Ashley, Jack H. Ashton, Arthur H. Asp, Joseph Atcheyman, Harry Atchison, Ernest Atencio, J.E. Atkins, George Atkinson, James W. Attaway, Glen LeRoy Attletweedt, Robert Atwood, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Marvin Aullman, Martin Aus, Perry Aus, Benjamin Austin, Ed Austin, James C. Austin (alias Jake Austin), Paul Austin, William Austin, Buck Avery, Joe C. Avila, Delmer G. Ayers, John Ayers, Kenneth Ayers, Thomas Charles Ayers, Vincent Ayers, Jimmie Ayres, Baptiste Azure, Bill Azure, Glen Azure, Joseph Azure, Joseph Angus Azure, Mary Azure, Max Azure, Max Azure, Marvin Gerald Azure, Richard M. Azure, Vern M. Azure, Walter J. Azure, William Azure, Kenneth Lee Baatz, Frank Jackson Babcock (alias Ryan Frank), M.M. Babcock (Murton Munroe Babcock), Max Baber, Ray D. Babich, Paul Babick, Paul Bachant, Joe Bachmeier, George Backer, Freddie Bacon, Leo Bad Boy, Ralph Badger, John Bagley, W.E. Bagley (alias Warren Eugene Bagley), W.J. Bagley (alias William J. Bagley), 1923-1960 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Joseph Bahm, Gordon Bahr, Betty Bailey, C.L. Bailey, Don F. Bailey, Donald Eugene Bailey, Ernest Bailey, Hammond Bailey, Irene Bailey, Jess Bailey, Lee Roy Bailey, Roger W. Bailey, Roy Lee Bailey, Walter R. Bailey, Ora Bain, Nelson Andrew Baird, Theodore Baird, Arthur Baker, Ben Baker, Dick Baker, Dolly Baker, Frank Baker, Frank Baker, Fred Baker, Frederick Levi Baker, Henry Baker, Homer Baker, Jack Baker, John Baker, Joseph B. Baker, Leo Baker, Louis Franklin Baker, Orville Baker, Raliegh A. Baker, Wallace Baker, Willie Baker, Hans .A. Bakke, Frank Balbi, Jan Balcer, Leo A. Balcom, James W. Baldwin (alias James Willis Baldwin), Melvin Baldwin, Edward F. Baler, Vola Bales, Frank Balkis, Albert J. Ball, Charles Ball, Richard Ball, Richard Ball (alias Donald C. LaMonte), Robert Ball, Charles D. Ballard, Jack Ballard, Ralph D. Ballard, Russell Ballard, Lewis B. Ballew, Victor Balli, Stephen Kells Balliet, Joe Baltazor, Clyde Ballard, Neevle H. Balton, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 56/7)